Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 3, Section 1: Boxes 1-22
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 3, Section 1: Boxes 1-22
- Box: 18, Folder: 97, Publication (Box 18, Folder 97)
  - Item 1: Performance and Review, 1965; Publication (Box 18, Folder 97)
- Box: 18, Folder: 98, Publication (Box 18, Folder 98)
  - Item 1: Employee Recruiting, 1965; Publication (Box 18, Folder 98)
- Box: 18, Folder: 99, Publication (Box 18, Folder 99)
  - Item 1: Interview Guide For General Factory and Office Section, 1965; Publication (Box 18, Folder 99)
- Box: 18, Folder: 100, Publication (Box 18, Folder 100)
  - Item 1: Employee Recruiting, 1965; Publication (Box 18, Folder 100)
- Box: 18, Folder: 101, Publication (Box 18, Folder 101)
  - Item 1: Employee Status Change, 1965; Publication (Box 18, Folder 101)
- Box: 18, Folder: 102, Publication (Box 18, Folder 102)
  - Item 1: Stockholders and Prices, 1950; Publication (Box 18, Folder 102)
- Box: 18, Folder: 103, Publication (Box 18, Folder 103)
  - Item 1: Employment Policy, 1948; Publication (Box 18, Folder 103)
- Box: 18, Folder: 104, Publication (Box 18, Folder 104)
  - Item 1: Management Training Program, 1962; Publication (Box 18, Folder 104)
- Box: 18, Folder: 105, Publication (Box 18, Folder 105)
  - Item 1: The Gillette Company Employees' Savings Plan, 1968; Publication (Box 18, Folder 105)
- Box: 18, Folder: 106, Publication (Box 18, Folder 106)
  - Item 1: Suggestion Systems, 1968; Publication (Box 18, Folder 106)
- Box: 18, Folder: 107, Publication (Box 18, Folder 107)
  - Item 1: Absenteeism, 1968; Publication (Box 18, Folder 107)
- Box: 18, Folder: 108, Publication (Box 18, Folder 108)
  - Item 1: Holiday Vacations, 1968; Publication (Box 18, Folder 108)
- Box: 18, Folder: 109, Publication (Box 18, Folder 109)
  - Item 1: Engineers, 1968; Publication (Box 18, Folder 109)
- Box: 18, Folder: 110, Publication (Box 18, Folder 110)
  - Item 1: Revised Organization Manuals, 1968; Publication (Box 18, Folder 110)
- Box: 19, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Personnel Evaluation, 1960; Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Box: 19, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Checkers Training Manual, 1969; Publication (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Box: 19, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Progress Record, Publication (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Box: 19, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Checkers Training Manual, 1969; Publication (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Box: 19, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Management Development Program, 1978; Publication (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Box: 19, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Training, 1978; Publication (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Box: 19, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Reviewing Management Performance In G.L.F., 1956; Publication (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Box: 19, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Management Seminar, 1956; Publication (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Box: 19, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Training, 1965; Publication (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Box: 19, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Handbook, Publication (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Box: 19, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Engineering Scholarship, 1954; Publication (Box 19, Folder 11)
- Box: 19, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Training, 1953; Publication (Box 19, Folder 12)
- Box: 19, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Introduction To Supervision, 1951; Publication (Box 19, Folder 13)
- Box: 19, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Goodyear Tire & Rubber Company, Publication (Box 19, Folder 14)
- Box: 19, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Office Management Conferences, 1954; Publication (Box 19, Folder 15)
- Box: 19, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Suggestion Systems, 1964; Publication (Box 19, Folder 16)
- Box: 19, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: General Policies, 1953; Publication (Box 19, Folder 17)
- Box: 19, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Employee's Retirement System, Publication (Box 19, Folder 18)
- Box: 19, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Selling & Marketing Opportunities In Heinz, 1964; Publication (Box 19, Folder 19)
- Box: 19, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Application For Employment, 1953; Publication (Box 19, Folder 20)
- Box: 19, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Supervisonal Training 1950-1951, Publication (Box 19, Folder 21)
- Box: 19, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: The Key To Results In Supervision, 1950; Publication (Box 19, Folder 22)
- Box: 19, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Pension Conference, 1950; Publication (Box 19, Folder 23)
- Box: 19, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Management Training Program, 1965; Publication (Box 19, Folder 24)
- Box: 19, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Job Rating, 1954; Publication (Box 19, Folder 25)
- Box: 19, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Safety Rating Plan, 1954; Publication (Box 19, Folder 26)
- Box: 19, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Employee Recruiting, 1962; Publication (Box 19, Folder 27)
- Box: 19, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Management Training Program, 1962; Publication (Box 19, Folder 28)
- Box: 19, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Operating Chart, 1965; Publication (Box 19, Folder 29)
- Box: 19, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Industrial Relations Forum, 1951; Publication (Box 19, Folder 30)
- Box: 19, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Industrial Relations Forum, 1950; Publication (Box 19, Folder 31)
- Box: 19, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Apprentice Training Program For High School Graduates, 1958; Publication (Box 19, Folder 32)
- Box: 19, Folder: 33, Publication (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Leadership Series 1954-55, 1958; Publication (Box 19, Folder 33)
- Box: 19, Folder: 34, Publication (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Face To Face Leadership, 1958; Publication (Box 19, Folder 34)
- Box: 19, Folder: 35, Publication (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Factory Manual Revision #58, 1950; Publication (Box 19, Folder 35)
- Box: 19, Folder: 36, Publication (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Supervisional Newsletter, 1950; Publication (Box 19, Folder 36)
- Box: 19, Folder: 37, Publication (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: Pension, Insurance and Service Award Agreement, 1955; Publication (Box 19, Folder 37)
- Box: 19, Folder: 38, Publication (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: Chapter XVI: Health, 1949; Publication (Box 19, Folder 38)
- Box: 19, Folder: 39, Publication (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: Pension, Insurance and Service Award Agreement, 1964; Publication (Box 19, Folder 39)
- Box: 19, Folder: 40, Publication (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: Chapter VIII: Exits and Transfers & Leaves of Absence, 1950; Publication (Box 19, Folder 40)
- Box: 19, Folder: 41, Publication (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: Employee Services, 1950; Publication (Box 19, Folder 41)
- Box: 19, Folder: 42, Publication (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - Item 1: Handbook: Job Talk, 1954; Publication (Box 19, Folder 42)
- Box: 19, Folder: 43, Publication (Box 19, Folder 43)
  - Item 1: Industrial Relations Forum, 1952; Publication (Box 19, Folder 43)
- Box: 19, Folder: 44, Publication (Box 19, Folder 44)
  - Item 1: Industrial Relations, 1957; Publication (Box 19, Folder 44)
- Box: 20, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Supervisor's Administrative Guide, 1967; Publication (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Box: 20, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Group Insurance, 1955; Publication (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Box: 20, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Group Insurance, 1964; Publication (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Box: 20, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Handbook, 1964; Publication (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Box: 20, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Group Life Insurance Plan, 1949; Publication (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Box: 20, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Here Is Your Death and Disability Benefits Package, 1959; Publication (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Box: 20, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Group Disability Insurance, 1959; Publication (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Box: 20, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Employees' Retirement Income Plan, 1959; Publication (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Box: 20, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Group Insurance, 1959; Publication (Box 20, Folder 9)
- Box: 20, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Group Insurance, 1953; Publication (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Box: 20, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Group Insurance, 1959; Publication (Box 20, Folder 11)
- Box: 20, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Group Insurance, 1957; Publication (Box 20, Folder 12)
- Box: 20, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Office Etiquette, 1956; Publication (Box 20, Folder 13)
- Box: 20, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Suggestion Systems, 1956; Publication (Box 20, Folder 14)
- Box: 20, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Handbook, 1953; Publication (Box 20, Folder 15)
- Box: 20, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Tuition Aid Plan, 1961; Publication (Box 20, Folder 16)
- Box: 20, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Employee's Retirement Income Plan, 1961; Publication (Box 20, Folder 17)
- Box: 20, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Major Medical Coverage, 1961; Publication (Box 20, Folder 18)
- Box: 20, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Group Insurance, 1961; Publication (Box 20, Folder 19)
- Box: 20, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Suggestion System, 1950; Publication (Box 20, Folder 20)
- Box: 20, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Safe Practices, 1950; Publication (Box 20, Folder 21)
- Box: 20, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Employee Recruiting, 1964; Publication (Box 20, Folder 22)
- Box: 20, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Business Promotion, 1969; Publication (Box 20, Folder 23)
- Box: 20, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Administrative Guide, 1976; Publication (Box 20, Folder 24)
- Box: 20, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Personal Practices and Procedures, 1966; Publication (Box 20, Folder 25)
- Box: 20, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Interviewer's Manual, 1961; Publication (Box 20, Folder 26)
- Box: 20, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Operating Methods Manual, 1953; Publication (Box 20, Folder 27)
- Box: 20, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Performance Definitions For Salary Administration, 1969; Publication (Box 20, Folder 28)
- Box: 20, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Consulting By Employees, 1969; Publication (Box 20, Folder 29)
- Box: 20, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Farmall Operator Training Manual, 1954; Publication (Box 20, Folder 30)
- Box: 20, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Truck Driver Training Program, 1954; Publication (Box 20, Folder 31)
- Box: 20, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Wage And Salary Administration, Publication (Box 20, Folder 32)
- Box: 20, Folder: 33, Publication (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Trade Union Program, 1957; Publication (Box 20, Folder 33)
- Box: 20, Folder: 34, Publication (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Training and Relocating, Publication (Box 20, Folder 34)
- Box: 20, Folder: 35, Publication (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Employee Recruiting, 1963; Publication (Box 20, Folder 35)
- Box: 20, Folder: 36, Publication (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Wage And Salary Administration, Publication (Box 20, Folder 36)
- Box: 20, Folder: 37, Publication (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: Wage And Salary Administration, Publication (Box 20, Folder 37)
- Box: 20, Folder: 38, Publication (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: Wage And Salary Administration, Publication (Box 20, Folder 38)
- Box: 20, Folder: 39, Publication (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: Wage And Salary Administration, Publication (Box 20, Folder 39)
- Box: 20, Folder: 40, Publication (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: Wage And Salary Administration, Publication (Box 20, Folder 40)
- Box: 20, Folder: 41, Publication (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: Education Program, 1966; Publication (Box 20, Folder 41)
- Box: 20, Folder: 42, Publication (Box 20, Folder 42)
  - Item 1: Outline For An Eight-Week Supervisory Training Program, 1958; Publication (Box 20, Folder 42)
- Box: 20, Folder: 43, Publication (Box 20, Folder 43)
  - Item 1: Bonus Point Plan, 1956; Publication (Box 20, Folder 43)
- Box: 20, Folder: 44, Publication (Box 20, Folder 44)
  - Item 1: A Bonus Point Plan For Employees, 1955; Publication (Box 20, Folder 44)
- Box: 20, Folder: 45, Publication (Box 20, Folder 45)
  - Item 1: Servicemen's Reinstatement Policy, 1965; Publication (Box 20, Folder 45)
- Box: 20, Folder: 46, Publication (Box 20, Folder 46)
  - Item 1: Opportunities For Engineers and Scientist, 1966; Publication (Box 20, Folder 46)
- Box: 20, Folder: 47, Publication (Box 20, Folder 47)
  - Item 1: Supervisor's Handbook, 1966; Publication (Box 20, Folder 47)
- Box: 20, Folder: 48, Publication (Box 20, Folder 48)
  - Item 1: Error-Free Performance, 1966; Publication (Box 20, Folder 48)
- Box: 20, Folder: 49, Publication (Box 20, Folder 49)
  - Item 1: Error Cause Removal Program, 1966; Publication (Box 20, Folder 49)
- Box: 20, Folder: 50, Publication (Box 20, Folder 50)
  - Item 1: Corporate Employee Relations Bulletins, 1969; Publication (Box 20, Folder 50)
- Box: 20, Folder: 51, Publication (Box 20, Folder 51)
  - Item 1: Corporate Employee Relations Relations Bulletins, 1969; Publication (Box 20, Folder 51)
- Box: 20, Folder: 52, Publication (Box 20, Folder 52)
  - Item 1: Sex Discrimination, 1968; Publication (Box 20, Folder 52)
- Box: 20, Folder: 53, Publication (Box 20, Folder 53)
  - Item 1: Interoffice Correspondence, 1969; Publication (Box 20, Folder 53)
- Box: 20, Folder: 54, Publication (Box 20, Folder 54)
  - Item 1: Trade Union Program, 1955; Publication (Box 20, Folder 54)
- Box: 20, Folder: 55, Publication (Box 20, Folder 55)
  - Item 1: Program On Technology and Society, 1965; Publication (Box 20, Folder 55)
- Box: 20, Folder: 56, Publication (Box 20, Folder 56)
  - Item 1: Research Center In Entrepreneurial History, 1962; Publication (Box 20, Folder 56)
- Box: 20, Folder: 57, Publication (Box 20, Folder 57)
  - Item 1: Wage Chronology: Sugar Industry, 1951; Publication (Box 20, Folder 57)
- Box: 20, Folder: 58, Publication (Box 20, Folder 58)
  - Item 1: Morale And Motivation Program, 1964; Publication (Box 20, Folder 58)
- Box: 20, Folder: 59, Publication (Box 20, Folder 59)
  - Item 1: Accident Prevention, 1952; Publication (Box 20, Folder 59)
- Box: 20, Folder: 60, Publication (Box 20, Folder 60)
  - Item 1: Employee Appraisal Plan, 1956; Publication (Box 20, Folder 60)
- Box: 20, Folder: 61, Publication (Box 20, Folder 61)
  - Item 1: Annual Review, 1951; Publication (Box 20, Folder 61)
- Box: 20, Folder: 62, Publication (Box 20, Folder 62)
  - Item 1: Employee Rating Form (Hourly Rated), 1951; Publication (Box 20, Folder 62)
- Box: 20, Folder: 63, Publication (Box 20, Folder 63)
  - Item 1: Proposed Industrial Relations Activities, 1952; Publication (Box 20, Folder 63)
- Box: 20, Folder: 64, Publication (Box 20, Folder 64)
  - Item 1: Employee Recruiting, 1963; Publication (Box 20, Folder 64)
- Box: 20, Folder: 65, Publication (Box 20, Folder 65)
  - Item 1: Medical Policy & Procedure, 1969; Publication (Box 20, Folder 65)
- Box: 20, Folder: 66, Publication (Box 20, Folder 66)
  - Item 1: Federal Conflict Of Interest Laws Relating To Former U.S. Officers and Civilian Employees, 1963; Publication (Box 20, Folder 66)
- Box: 20, Folder: 67, Publication (Box 20, Folder 67)
  - Item 1: Subcontracting and Work Removal, 1965; Publication (Box 20, Folder 67)
- Box: 20, Folder: 68, Publication (Box 20, Folder 68)
  - Item 1: Advertising In Labor Publications, 1963; Publication (Box 20, Folder 68)
- Box: 20, Folder: 69, Publication (Box 20, Folder 69)
  - Item 1: Exempt/ Non-Exempt Determination Forms For Classifying Employees, 1963; Publication (Box 20, Folder 69)
- Box: 20, Folder: 70, Publication (Box 20, Folder 70)
  - Item 1: Cerb. No. 9 Revision, 1969; Publication (Box 20, Folder 70)
- Box: 20, Folder: 71, Publication (Box 20, Folder 71)
  - Item 1: Correction To Cerb #9 EEOC, 1969; Publication (Box 20, Folder 71)
- Box: 20, Folder: 72, Publication (Box 20, Folder 72)
  - Item 1: E.E.O.C., 1969; Publication (Box 20, Folder 72)
- Box: 20, Folder: 73, Publication (Box 20, Folder 73)
  - Item 1: Agreements To Agree, 1963; Publication (Box 20, Folder 73)
- Box: 20, Folder: 74, Publication (Box 20, Folder 74)
  - Item 1: Required Notices of Termination of Collective Bargaining Agreements, 1963; Publication (Box 20, Folder 74)
- Box: 20, Folder: 75, Publication (Box 20, Folder 75)
  - Item 1: Political Activity By Employers, 1974; Publication (Box 20, Folder 75)
- Box: 20, Folder: 76, Publication (Box 20, Folder 76)
  - Item 1: Extended Vacation Leave Of Absence, 1968; Publication (Box 20, Folder 76)
- Box: 20, Folder: 77, Publication (Box 20, Folder 77)
  - Item 1: Medical Examinations For Employees Working After Age 65, 1968; Publication (Box 20, Folder 77)
- Box: 20, Folder: 78, Publication (Box 20, Folder 78)
  - Item 1: Investigations and Charges, 1967; Publication (Box 20, Folder 78)
- Box: 20, Folder: 79, Publication (Box 20, Folder 79)
  - Item 1: Union Requests, 1965; Publication (Box 20, Folder 79)
- Box: 20, Folder: 80, Publication (Box 20, Folder 80)
  - Item 1: Use Of The State Employment Service, 1964; Publication (Box 20, Folder 80)
- Box: 20, Folder: 81, Publication (Box 20, Folder 81)
  - Item 1: Death Benefits, 1969; Publication (Box 20, Folder 81)
- Box: 20, Folder: 82, Publication (Box 20, Folder 82)
  - Item 1: Safety Regulations, 1964; Publication (Box 20, Folder 82)
- Box: 20, Folder: 83, Publication (Box 20, Folder 83)
  - Item 1: Relocation Expense Reimbursement Practice, 1969; Publication (Box 20, Folder 83)
- Box: 20, Folder: 84, Publication (Box 20, Folder 84)
  - Item 1: Trade Secrets, 1964; Publication (Box 20, Folder 84)
- Box: 20, Folder: 85, Publication (Box 20, Folder 85)
  - Item 1: Employment of Relatives, 1966; Publication (Box 20, Folder 85)
- Box: 20, Folder: 86, Publication (Box 20, Folder 86)
  - Item 1: Religious Practice Accommodation, 1968; Publication (Box 20, Folder 86)
- Box: 20, Folder: 87, Publication (Box 20, Folder 87)
  - Item 1: Sale of Honeywell Merchandise To Retired Personnel, 1965; Publication (Box 20, Folder 87)
- Box: 20, Folder: 88, Publication (Box 20, Folder 88)
  - Item 1: Garnishment Handling, 1965; Publication (Box 20, Folder 88)
- Box: 20, Folder: 89, Publication (Box 20, Folder 89)
  - Item 1: Salary Continuation Plan, 1965; Publication (Box 20, Folder 89)
- Box: 20, Folder: 90, Publication (Box 20, Folder 90)
  - Item 1: Safety and Industrial Hygiene, 1965; Publication (Box 20, Folder 90)
- Box: 20, Folder: 91, Publication (Box 20, Folder 91)
  - Item 1: Transfer of Non-Exempt Employees Between Honeywell Divisions, 1965; Publication (Box 20, Folder 91)
- Box: 20, Folder: 92, Publication (Box 20, Folder 92)
  - Item 1: Manpower Planning & Development Policy, 1965; Publication (Box 20, Folder 92)
- Box: 20, Folder: 93, Publication (Box 20, Folder 93)
  - Item 1: College Recruiting Program, 1965; Publication (Box 20, Folder 93)
- Box: 20, Folder: 94, Publication (Box 20, Folder 94)
  - Item 1: Servicemen's Reinstatement Policy, 1968; Publication (Box 20, Folder 94)
- Box: 20, Folder: 95, Publication (Box 20, Folder 95)
  - Item 1: Jury Duty, 1965; Publication (Box 20, Folder 95)
- Box: 20, Folder: 96, Publication (Box 20, Folder 96)
  - Item 1: Service Contract Act- Revised Regulations, 1968; Publication (Box 20, Folder 96)
- Box: 20, Folder: 97, Publication (Box 20, Folder 97)
  - Item 1: Records- Interdivisional Transfers, 1966; Publication (Box 20, Folder 97)
- Box: 20, Folder: 98, Publication (Box 20, Folder 98)
  - Item 1: Intercompany Transfers Pension and Other Benefit Plans, 1966; Publication (Box 20, Folder 98)
- Box: 20, Folder: 99, Publication (Box 20, Folder 99)
  - Item 1: College Relations- Resourcing, 1966; Publication (Box 20, Folder 99)
- Box: 20, Folder: 100, Publication (Box 20, Folder 100)
  - Item 1: Industrial Hygiene Equipment, 1966; Publication (Box 20, Folder 100)
- Box: 20, Folder: 101, Publication (Box 20, Folder 101)
  - Item 1: Collective Bargaining - Reference To Competitive Position of Ability To Pay, 1966; Publication (Box 20, Folder 101)
- Box: 20, Folder: 102, Publication (Box 20, Folder 102)
  - Item 1: Unused Vacation For Transferred Employees, 1966; Publication (Box 20, Folder 102)
- Box: 20, Folder: 103, Publication (Box 20, Folder 103)
  - Item 1: Immunization Against Communicable Diseases, 1967; Publication (Box 20, Folder 103)
- Box: 20, Folder: 104, Publication (Box 20, Folder 104)
  - Item 1: Employment Agency Fees- Possible Tax Implications, 1966; Publication (Box 20, Folder 104)
- Box: 20, Folder: 105, Publication (Box 20, Folder 105)
  - Item 1: Sale Of Honeywell Products To Employees, 1968; Publication (Box 20, Folder 105)
- Box: 20, Folder: 106, Publication (Box 20, Folder 106)
  - Item 1: Aid To Education - Gifts of Surplus Materials and Equipment, 1966; Publication (Box 20, Folder 106)
- Box: 20, Folder: 107, Publication (Box 20, Folder 107)
  - Item 1: Service or Process Of Arrest of Employees On Company Premises, 1966; Publication (Box 20, Folder 107)
- Box: 20, Folder: 108, Publication (Box 20, Folder 108)
  - Item 1: Procedure For Changing Engineering Non-Supervisory and Supervisory Position Slotting, 1966; Publication (Box 20, Folder 108)
- Box: 20, Folder: 109, Publication (Box 20, Folder 109)
  - Item 1: Foreign Service Policy For Permanent and Temporary Assignment, 1966; Publication (Box 20, Folder 109)
- Box: 20, Folder: 110, Publication (Box 20, Folder 110)
  - Item 1: Occupational Deferments, 1967; Publication (Box 20, Folder 110)
- Box: 20, Folder: 111, Publication (Box 20, Folder 111)
  - Item 1: Solicitation, Distribution, and Bulletin Board Rules, 1966; Publication (Box 20, Folder 111)
- Box: 20, Folder: 112, Publication (Box 20, Folder 112)
  - Item 1: Political Campaigning, 1967; Publication (Box 20, Folder 112)
- Box: 20, Folder: 113, Publication (Box 20, Folder 113)
  - Item 1: Outside Business Interests, 1967; Publication (Box 20, Folder 113)
- Box: 20, Folder: 114, Publication (Box 20, Folder 114)
  - Item 1: Malpractice Liability, 1967; Publication (Box 20, Folder 114)
- Box: 20, Folder: 115, Publication (Box 20, Folder 115)
  - Item 1: Personnel Files of Personnel Managers, 1967; Publication (Box 20, Folder 115)
- Box: 20, Folder: 116, Publication (Box 20, Folder 116)
  - Item 1: Releasing Information On Employees and Former Employees, 1968; Publication (Box 20, Folder 116)
- Box: 20, Folder: 117, Publication (Box 20, Folder 117)
  - Item 1: Travel Time- Paying Non-Exempt Employees, 1967; Publication (Box 20, Folder 117)
- Box: 20, Folder: 118, Publication (Box 20, Folder 118)